CONTACT



0468585718 mr.john.coote@gmail.com @johnofsydney www.linkedin.com/in/mrjohncoote/ johnofsydney.github.io/professionalIntroduction/

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Web Development Immersive October 2017 - January 2018

SYDNEY UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering

SUMMARY

I have several years of work experience in Electrical Engineering and Recruitment. I recently decided to re-train and make a career in web development.

I am seeking a junior web developer position in either full stack or back end development. I'm open to any kind of work environment that will allow me to further develop my skills.

EXPERIENCE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Student. October 2017 - January 2018 Full time course covering an introduction to progamming, databases and various technologies required for junior full stack developer

DATAHOUSESOFTWARE

Design and Development. 2006 - present At the same time as I was running my recruitment business I developed and sold a recruitment database "Pipeline" suitable for running a small recruitment agency. Pipeline has been used by companies in Australia, NZ, UK, USA and South Africa. It is still available as freeware but I'm no longer actively developing new features. www.datahousesoftware.com

EMERSON

Electrical Engineer. 2014 - 2015 Design, Production Engineering, Testing and Commissioning of standby power systems for the telecommunications industry

STAFFORD ISLAND

Business Owner 2006 - 2014 A recruitment agency sourcing candidates for the electrical engineering industry. My role covered business development, account management, advertising, wages, taxes, insurance. During the busiest years I had contractors in 3 states and a wage bill of ~\$900k pa .as well as making placements for permanent positions.

 Ruby & Rails Postegresal Sinatra React APIs & JSON Bootstrap • git/github

COMMAND RECRUITMENT

Consultant, 2004 - 2006 Contract and permanent recruiting for the electrical engineering industry

ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

Design, Production Engineering, Project Management, Testing and Commissioning of stand by power systems for the telecommunications industry. Most of my work was for a company called Com10 who are no longer in business.

OLD SKILLS

NEW SKILLS

• JQuery & underscore

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

- Small Business Management
- New Business Development
- MS Access / VBA
- MS SOL Server
- Translating business requirements into software
- Engineering Design (AutoCAD) and Project Management
- · On site testing and commissioning
- Technical presentation

Referees: on request